Next Episode Preview
Thank you for watching!
Tears on a bruised day?
Not in vain.
I'm finally at the stage where I've arrived.
You know what I'm talking about
Make you laugh, make me laugh
I'll sing, I'll sing, I'll sing for joy, I'll sing for joy, I'll sing for joy
My heart is shaken, my heart is broken
My friends will heal it
Rough Rough Members 2-shot Talk
And today's guest is this person
Mika Fujisaki.
Please.
This time, Yui Yui, who was supposed to ask a question, is absent due to illness.
Sasaki will be on the dais.
Thank you very much.
Let's start reading your answers.
The first question is "What was your impression when you first saw the show?
First of all, Miri's answer was very blunt.
Yes, it was during the screening that I saw Miri.
It says that she was shocked to see someone wearing a blunt piece of paper at the audition.
I feel sorry for her.
I may have changed the rules of auditioning.
It was your last audition.
It turned out all right, didn't it?
Then Meinya, who I met for the first time at the audition... how old is she?
She looked so young. I felt overwhelmingly younger than her, and I was worried.
I'm not an old lady, but you're not an old lady, Meinya.
I'm not an old lady!
Next was Haruren, a very shy girl.
She's really quiet and shy, like an elementary school student.
Isn't that what Haruren says?
She was quiet too, wasn't she?
After what they showed us in the third round...
I'm not talking about the quiet one, I'm talking about Harren.
Why would you call him a quiet elementary school student?
During the audition, you were told not to get involved with the other kids.
That's all I did.
I see.
He said it would be awkward if you were close to them if you didn't get accepted.
I see. Who told you that?
It was an idol friend of mine.
I see.
Next, we took a survey asking you to describe yourself in one word.
Here's Ryoka's answer.
Twintails are the strongest idol, Miku Fujisaki, who will save the world.
She's cute!
What's your catchphrase?
I am.
I'm a girl who dreams big and works hard with all her might.
When I see someone like Miku who has ambitions and works hard, I feel like I have to work hard too.
Torn?
But I say that a lot on LINE, don't I?
Yeah, I do.
Not on LINE, not in the past, but in letters.
Yeah, in letters, too.
I do.
Long sentences.
You read it.You read it.
I have some left.
Then we'll continue.
Here you go.
Next up is Yui Yui.
Fantasy.
I have a realistic mindset, but when I'm excited and excited, I'm so sparkly and cute, it's like I'm in a dream world.
Fantasy
You've done it!
Next, Arisa Saito.
Neighborhood elementary school students
The neighborhood elementary school kids... they're talking happily all the time... in a good way to me.
In a good way.
But so far... three people have called me an elementary schooler.
Right?
They're so young.
Yes, they are.
Oh, no.
Elementary school.
I'm a senior in high school.
Go on, then.
Who is the Miku that only you know? Here's the questionnaire.
First of all, I'd like to introduce Monami.
The week of Ryoka's and my birthday, she drew a portrait of us on her insta-story.
I noticed it too.
Really?
You noticed? It was just a picture I drew in a few seconds, so I didn't think anyone would notice.
But Monami responded to the story.
Really?
You're good at drawing.
Thank you.
Next.
Hello.
When you post a two-shot or something on social networking sites, can I post this? I ask.
No, I'll hide my pores.
I'll hide my pores.
Don't worry, you have beautiful, smooth skin.
What?
Oh, my God.
I love it!
I love you, but you know what, I hide my pores every time.
I do it every time.
That's a must.
That's the only thing I'm asking you to do.
Then, please have everyone remember that.
Next, Miri.
In the very beginning, we were dashing together in Shibuya, and Miri's shoe was broken.
That was the day we all remembered each other,
We were running in Shibuya, and my shoe was broken, so I had to take it off many times.
And I was like, "I'm leaving Miri behind.
Running? And Miri was so tongue-tied.
Oh my God!
We used to do that.
I remember those days.
It was the very beginning, wasn't it?
Yes, it was the very beginning.
Next, I'd like to ask, "What is the best part of Miku? Next, I'd like to ask you what you think is great about Miku.Next, I would like to ask, "What is the best part of Miku? I'll start with me.
First of all, I'll start with me.
I'm kind of embarrassed.
You're not embarrassed?
I am embarrassed.
Let me start.
Through the activities, I am able to communicate my feelings more and more honestly to others.
I am a person who can no longer speak, so even if my Japanese is not good, I am able to remember and convey my feelings honestly.
I am told that my Japanese is not good.
It's said casually, and it's coming from his own mouth.
But with emphasis on the fact that he is not a good Japanese speaker.
Well, you know.
Thank you.
Double turn.
I'll get embarrassed.
Okay, next, Manami.
I'm amazed at how stoically she tackles everything with all her might.
I've seen her practice a single dance move over and over again until she was satisfied with it.
Double turn.
Then let's keep going like this.
Yui yui.
The careful attention you give to each and every job.
Even when filming for TikTok, you take more time than anyone else to redo it until you find your best. I think that's great and amazing.
When you get shy, how do you react?
Why are you so invisible?
I don't know, makeup.
What should I do?
Should I just say I'm embarrassed?
Where's the embarrassment?
There are a lot of members who say that seeing Miku working hard makes them want to work hard together.
That's great.
I'm glad.
Next, what do you honestly want me to fix?
Oh no. This is what I'm afraid of. This is what I've always been afraid of.
Hanerun.
It's a little hard to understand the human nature of things like LINE when communicating with individuals.
Or expressing a class as a class,
Please" for "please.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't get it.
When I have time, I feel like I'm solving a riddle,
You should use Japanese once in a while.
I just got on the phone with you today,
Lately, I've been reducing the size of Harurun and Yo, and everything else that can be made smaller.
I'm getting smaller, aren't I?
Yeah, I know.
Like, "It's okay," "It's okay.
Like that.
It's getting better.
We're close.
It's OK.
Then I'm going to be a good friend, too,
I'm going to solve the riddle with a happy heart.
OK.
Next.
No, no, no. Your eyelashes are too long, too beautiful, and I envy you, so I want you to share some of them with me.No, no, no. I want you to share some of your eyelashes because they are too long, too beautiful, and too enviable.
And while you're at it, I'd like you to share your abs, too.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You have abs?
No, no, no, no, not recently.
Not recently?
Assuming you don't have any recently,
I have two arisaacs.
What? Oh, no.
The first one.
Please stop finding the slightest mistake and teasing me about it.
They give you a story about a little misspoken word.
Please do something about it.
You repeat yourself a lot, Mikuni.
Really, you're laughing all the time.
You make mistakes like you're doing something really cool,
So I want to share and share with you.
On the other hand, if I don't share, Miku will be in the background forever, and if I don't share, I won't be able to stop laughing.
Second.
Please stop telling me every time I walk home or when I'm walking home that I'm walking too slow.
I just said that earlier.
You said it earlier.
You're right, I do say it every time.
Because I'm going over.
I thought you left first.
That's right.
Please stop saying it every time.
Yes, I do.
And there are two maidea as well.
The man who asks Dossinia for life advice.
I don't mind if you consult with him at all,
Doshinia is really too doshinia.
Please go to bed early, high school student.
You're still awake.
What time do you ask for advice?
2:00 or 3:00?
You're a senior, aren't you?
But Maidia comes home.
She's awake.
Yes, she is. But, you know, it's a last resort when you can't sleep if you don't solve the problem.
She's definitely awake.
I'm awake, I'm almost sure of it.
Second.
Please don't go all in on me.
You know all my old activities and embarrassing things.
It's to the point where I'm afraid of how you know so much.
But thank you.
But I found out about Ueno-chan when I was living,
She's so cute, you just want to know her, don't you?
I often say, "Stop asking me how I know you, even when I'm practicing.
I do. Mena-chan.
As the best.
You know why she's the best, that's why she does what she does. I'm sure.
How about asking her what she wants me to fix?
Especially after Arisachi and Mei, I got two points up.
They went up by 2 points each.
I'll leave Mena's alone for now,
Arisachi's is bad that the second last one is too slow.
She is rebelling.
It's bad to be slow. Leader.It's bad that it's so slow. Leader.
The last question is something I want to say since I'm here.
Natsume & Hayashi, let's have a yakiniku revenge with the yakiniku kids.
We're covered.
You mean you both have the same name?
That's amazing.
The Yakiniku Kids activity has been postponed,
I can't do it if I don't go.
I'm shaking.
Then, please take revenge.
Arisachi asked me if I knew how to read the lyrics in English,
Please study English so that you can read it.
There is a new song in English,
I don't know how to read it,
I guess I could just Google it,
I know you can do it on Google, but I wanted you to write it in Japanese,
I wanted it to be written in Japanese, like "Apple" would be written in Japanese.
I wanted them to write it in Japanese, like "Apple" for Apple,
I asked Arisachi to write it in Japanese.
I asked her to send me a message or something.
I asked her to tell me how to write in hiragana and Japanese,
I asked her to teach me hiragana and Japanese,
Arisachi sent me everything.
She is so kind.
She's very kind, but I should certainly study English.
I'll do it.
Next, Munami.
I finally started watching Oshiko, which Miku-chan recommended.
I now understand what Miku-chan meant when she told me to watch it hundreds of times.
Really?
I'm sorry I've been a "watch it again" scam for so long.
He's looking at me, and I'm still a scammer.
Then, maybe it's Mumin.
Since Miku said "Mirumiru Mirai Fraud," you went to the trouble of reporting that you saw it, didn't you?
That's right. That's good.
But many YAFU-YAKA members started watching Osashiko because of Miku, didn't they?
That's right.
Also, it's because it's popular.
The OshiNoko event has become more popular than I expected.
That's great.
I'm so happy. We can share what we like.
I guess so.
Next, Yui Yui.
I want to go with you for a personal color diagnosis, face type diagnosis, and skeletal structure diagnosis next time.
I've been meaning to ask Miku out since about 3 months ago, but she always forgets, so I used the Tokyo airwaves to invite her.
I'm sure my fans will remember me, and I'm sure I won't forget this promise again.
They said they want to go.
I'd love to.
Wanna go?
I wish I could take you with me.
Well, let's all go.
The nine of us.
Nine?
You want to barge in?
We'll barge in.
I feel sorry for him. The one who checks.
For nine people.
We're a little short-handed.
I'm going to be told.
So, this was your first foodie talk, how was it?So, this was my first foodie talk, how was it?
Basically, warm comments.
Basically.
I asked him to stop saying that.
That's all they said.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm glad. I was afraid that they would say, "Please don't exist," or "Please don't do this.
That's not true.
I thought they would tell me not to talk to them at times like this.
I'm glad.
Yes, I'm glad. They did.
But no one would say that, right?
That's right.
I'm glad.
He did it.
Now that we are in the two-year format, is there any member you would like to interview next?
Himinomeina.
Yay!
That's right.
Next up is Miku and Meyna's foodie talk.
That's all for the member relay talk.
Yay! Thank you very much.
You there, who have finished watching the video!
You watched it to the end. I'm so glad!
What do you think? Did you enjoy it?
Wait a minute. You didn't subscribe to our channel?
I can't believe it!
It only takes a second to hit the subscribe button!
Come on, Monomi!
You're a subscriber, you're a subscriber, you're a Saimin!
Thank you, you hit the subscribe button.
Thank you for subscribing!